having a powerful grip strength can go a
long way when weightlifting and playing
sports but you know it also plays an
important role in our everyday lives
well you can always test your grip
strength by seeing how many bags of
groceries you can handle in one trip
from the car to the house having a grip
strengthener like one of these from
living fit allows you to train those
same muscles without as much effort
required I've been using these bad boys
quite a bit lately we got a fun one
today so let's go ahead and get to it
[Music]
what's up my people it's Jake back in
the barbing garage gym and for today's
video I've got some grip strengtheners
from livingfit that I'm going to be
reviewing for you guys now in this video
I'm gonna tell you everything you need
to know about this product from the
price and some of the features it has
some pros and cons and of course who
should or maybe should not purchase
these but before I get going with all
that we've reviewed a whole lot of grip
strengtheners on barbin.com so if you
want to browse our best list all you
gotta do is search barvin best drip
strengtheners our list is going to pull
up for you and you can find out which
one cracks that number one spot
[Music]
okay so let's take a second and talk
about what I like about these grip
strengtheners from living fit and
honestly the first thing that came to
mind was just simplicity at its finest
so all you do is grab one of these bad
boys in your hand start squeezing it's
all there is to it now I also really
enjoy the aluminum knurled handles gives
me a really solid grip you know all of
them are knurled like that and it's just
a really nice touch I also like this
these carbon steel Springs you know
really durable and both of these
materials are going to be pretty
resistant to rust which is a nice thing
for obvious reasons these are
competitively priced so they're all
going to run you around 20 bucks and
speaking of the multiple options there's
four different ones you can choose from
100 pounds 150 pounds 200 and I don't
have the 250 on me right now but you
know it's really nice knowing that
there's these different options it's
going to allow most people to find one
that suits their needs the best
[Music]
all right so let's go ahead and talk
about a few cons I guess you might run
into but honestly guys like I can't
really think of any so if we want to
gripe about money I mean yeah there's
some cheaper ones out there around 10
bucks maybe even less than that but
those are probably made of plastic they
might not even last you very long so
honestly 20 bucks is
pretty pretty solid in my opinion and
other than that though honestly it's
probably just the knurling you know
textures personal preference and you
might not necessarily like that so
definitely just keep that in mind
okay so let's take a quick second and
talk about some money and there's not a
whole lot going on here because this is
really straightforward so every single
one of these grip strengtheners are
going to run you right around 20 bucks
it's really competitive compared to you
know other similar products that are on
the market and you know there's not a
designated full set for you to purchase
on the living fit website but you know
you can purchase all four of them for
around 80 bucks which is also a really
good deal it's actually cheaper than
some other options that I was browsing
online the other day and you know that's
really nice yes you can absolutely find
some cheaper ones out there that are
made of plastic but honestly you know
considering the quality and kind of what
you're getting out of these in the long
run I think the money is more than
Justified
[Music]
so when it comes to the build and the
features of these grip strengtheners I
just want y'all to remember this is a
simple product so there's not a whole
lot going on but you know me I gotta
talk about it and I want to talk about
the handles first once again these are
fully narrowed made out of aluminum you
know it gives me a really solid grip
when I'm working on my grip which is
nice now I like how they used carbon
steel for the spring it's really durable
and you know that aluminum and the
carbon steel they're both going to
resist rust and corrosion at a pretty
you know efficient level so that's
pretty nice and then lastly I mean
that's pretty much it you have markings
that go on the bottom right here just to
show you you know what resistance you're
working with
okay so there's not a whole lot going on
here guys in terms of this demo but it's
me so I got to do it right so go ahead
and grab this hundred pound right here
and as you can see you do in fact have
your markings right there I'll go and
show you there's the 150 so I got it
upside down and then you got the 200
right here as well so you always know
you know which one you're going to grab
which is nice now it's really simple you
know you have your aluminum knurled
handle it's going to give you a really
solid grip and then you got your carbon
steel Spring right here which is highly
highly durable now it's a really simple
thing you know all you do is you want to
try to get these two handles to touch so
you just squeeze as you can see you know
like it's working my forearm underneath
right here and on the side and it's
going to work your wrist a little bit
too so it's gonna basically work
everything even your hands so you're
going to be able to strengthen all of
that so once you feel like you know it's
time to progress that's why you buy more
than one and you go ahead and get this
151 for example and you go ahead and
start squeezing now I'm not quite ready
for that 200 pound one yet I'm not gonna
lie to you guys I'll go ahead and try it
and go and show you that I still have a
way to go with that but it's nice that
you know you can purchase all four and
kind of you know progressively overload
your group stream
so let's talk about the people who might
want to purchase these living fit grip
strengtheners and honestly guys if
you're serious about increasing your
grip strength and your forearm strength
it's one of the best options in my
opinion trust me you're going to be
feeling the burn especially you know as
you go up and wait speaking of weight
there's four different options for you
to choose some remember 100 150 200 250
pounds so there's likely you know a
resistance for everybody out there and
also I mean once again this is just
simplicity at its finest you know all
you do sit here and hold it and squeeze
it and that's my opinion is an upgrade
compared to the other ones where you
have to lace up your fingers and expand
your hand and stuff like that so that's
cool too
[Music]
now when it comes to those who you know
might not want to purchase these grip
strengtheners it's honestly just
personal preference in my opinion you
know let's say you don't like the
knurling here well there's other options
that you know have a different knurling
pattern or maybe don't have knurling
whatsoever so definitely check that out
a lot of people also prefer the reverse
grip strengtheners like I was just
talking about where you lace up your
fingers and kind of expand your hand and
also you know if there's strengtheners
that are designed specifically for your
wrist you know where you kind of like
roll it up so honestly you know if you
know you're looking for one of those
specific options like I just mentioned
well you'll just have to keep looking
for you guys today on the living fit
grip strengtheners I personally love
this product super easy for me to use I
really like the knurling pattern right
here it gives me a really nice grip
there's multiple buying options which is
really nice for obvious reasons you know
there's a option for everybody and also
these are competitively priced they're
all going to run here on 20 bucks or 80
for the full package just remember
throwing pattern might not be ideal for
everybody and then also you know there's
different styles as I mentioned earlier
so this style right here might not be
the best for everybody out there or
really what everybody's looking for
thanks for watching y'all hope this
video was really helpful and I was able
to break down everything you need to
know about this product right here in
front of me as always stay tuned for my
next video but for now head over to
barbin.com because we have a full
written review about these grip
strengtheners all you got to do is
search bar Bend living fit grip
strengthen and review it's going to pull
right up for you you can read about
everything we talked about here today
I'll catch y'all next time
[Music]
thank you